American Posters from the World Wars
Vernon Historical Society
American Posters from the World Wars
1917-1918, 1941-1945
3.05 Map case, 3 drawers
Vernon Historical Society
The collection contains posters created during World War I and World War II for display on the Home Front. Themes include encouraging the purchase of war bonds, supporting those in battle and suggesting ways that people at home could help the war effort.
Restrictions
Collection open for research.
Acquisition Information
Many of these posters were collected by Stephen Von Euw during World War II and were part of the collection left to the Vernon Historical Society by his daughter. The rest of the posters came to the Society from individual donors over the years.
Biography
The posters were collected by people from Vernon and Rockville during both World Wars. Most of the World War II posters came from the Von Euw collection. As editor of The Rockville Journal during the war, Mr. Von Euw received posters from different government agencies. Mindful of their value as history and art, he saved them after the war.
Scope and Content of Collection
This collection of posters were published during World War I and World War II. The intended audience was the American public. Themes of the posters include promoting the sale of war bonds to finance the war, encouraging enlistment into the armed forces, encouraging support for the war effort, warning the public about hidden dangers and educating them about strategies to assist in the war effort. The posters vary in size. Many have illustrations in color. Several artists of note designed some of the posters. This collection reveals how the wars were presented to the public. In addition to being works of art, the posters show use of color and imagery presented in graphic style to stir the emotions as well as educate the public to the challenges of wartime.
Arrangement
The collection is stored in two drawers within a flat file cabinet. The posters are arranged in the order that they were accessioned.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
World War, 1917-1918- Connecticut- Rockville; World War, 1917-1918- Connecticut- Vernon; World War, 1917-1918- Posters; World War, 1939-1945- Connecticut- Rockville; World War,1939-1945- Connecticut- Vernon; World War,1939-1945- Posters; Von Euw, Stephen, 1896-1955; The Rockville Journal, Rockville, Connecticut; Posters
Separated Material
Some of the posters were part of the Von Euw collection which includes letters and correspondence from those in military service and documents and letters to and from Mr. Von Euw during World War II.
- World War I
  - Victory Liberty Loan, 1918; Size (in inches): 40 x 32; Publisher: Edwards & Deutsch Litho Co. Chicago; Gerrit A. Beneker (Box FD 7, Folder F1)
  - American Legion, undated; Size (in inches): 40 x 30; Publisher: Carey Print. (Box FD 7, Folder F1)
  - Liberty Loan, undated; Size (in inches): 40 x 29; Publisher: Ketterlinus (Box FD 7, Folder F1)
  - War Camp Community Services, 1918; Size (in inches): 42 x 28; M. Leon Bracker (Box FD 7, Folder F1)
  - Red Cross, undated; Size (in inches): 30 x 20; Publisher: American Lithographic Co. (Box FD 7, Folder F1)
  - Liberty Bonds - Lincoln, undated; Size (in inches): 30 x 20 (Box FD 7, Folder F1)
  - 3rd Liberty Loan, undated; Size (in inches): 30 x 20 1/4; Publisher: Sackett & Wilhelm, NY (Box FD 7, Folder F8)
  - 3rd Liberty Loan soldier, undated; Size (in inches): 30 x 20; Publisher: Sackett & Wilhelm, NY; Lawrence Harris (Box FD 7, Folder F8)
  - Halt the Hun, undated; Size (in inches): 29 1/2 x 20; Publisher: Edwards & Deutsch Litho Co. Chicago; Leach? (Box FD 7, Folder F8)
  - Over the Top, undated; Size (in inches): 30 X 20; Publisher: Ketterlinus; Sidney Riesenberg (Box FD 7, Folder F8)
  - Jewish Welfare Board, 1918; Size (in inches): 33 x 22; Sidney Riesenberg - Mylar (Box FD 7, Folder F14)
  - Work for Civilians (170), undated; Size (in inches): 30 x 20; Publisher: War Work Campaign (Box FD 7, Folder F15)
  1
  - Victory Stamps (Goddess), undated; Size (in inches): 30 x 20; Haskell Coffin (Box FD 7, Folder F15)
  - YMCA (Services), undated; Size (in inches): 30 x 20; Publisher: Committee on Public Information; Arthur William Brown (Box FD 7, Folder F15)
  - Books for Soldiers, 1918; Size (in inches): 30 x 20; Publisher: Committee on Public Information; Sheridan (Box FD 7, Folder F15)
  - War Camp (piano), undated; Size (in inches): 30 x 20; Publisher: Heywood Strauser & Voight Litho Co., NY (Box FD 7, Folder F15)
  - War Camp (Dinner), undated; Size (in inches): 35 x 20; Publisher: Heywood Strauser & Voight Litho Co., NY (Box FD 7, Folder F15)
  - Victory Loan, undated; Size (in inches): 2-11x7, 1-21x14 (Box FD 7, Folder F15)
  - Liberty Loan (Children), 1917; Size (in inches): 30 x 20; Publisher: T.F. Moore CO., NY (Box FD 7, Folder F15)
  - War Bonds - Wilson, undated; Size (in inches): 30 x 20; Publisher: American Lithographic Co., NY (Box FD 7, Folder F15)
  - Liberty Loan (Sailor & Soldier), 1917; Size (in inches): 30 x 20; Publisher: Edwards & Deutsch Litho Co. Chicago (Box FD 7, Folder F15)
  - Red Cross Service Flag, 1918; Size (in inches): 25 x 21; Publisher: Forbes Boston; Jessie Wilcox Smith (Box FD 7, Folder F15)
  - Liberty Loan - 100%, undated; Size (in inches): 30 x 20; Publisher: Sackett & Wilhelm, NY; Stern (Box FD 7, Folder F15)
  - Motor Transport Corps, 1919; Size (in inches): 25 x 19; Publisher: U.S. Army; George Carlson (Box FD 7, Folder F15)
  - War Fund Week (1st 3), undated; Size (in inches): 27 1/2 x 30 1/2; Kidder (Box FD 7, Folder F15)
  - YMCA/YWCA, undated; Size (in inches): 21 1/2 x 41 (Box FD 7, Folder F15)
  - Liberty Bonds, undated; Size (in inches): 1-28x22, 3-11x7 (Box FD 7, Folder F15)
  - Victory Stamps (Goddess), undated; Size (in inches): 42 x 28; Haskell Coffin (Box FD 7, Folder F15)
  - Red Cross (Battle Scene), undated; Size (in inches): 25 x 38; Publisher: Thomsen-Ellis Co., NY; Dan Smith (Box FD 7, Folder F15)
  - "Carry On" (WSS), undated; Size (in inches): 40 x 28 3/4; Dorothy Clayton (Box FD 7, Folder F15)
  - Buy Liberty Bonds (bulls eye), undated; Size (in inches): 28 1/4 x 22; Publisher: S.L Bush; Mylar (Box FD 7, Folder F17)
  - Red Cross Annual Call, undated; Size (in inches): 7 x 21; Mylar (Box FD 7, Folder F17)
  - Liberty Loan Banner, undated; Size (in inches): 10 3/4 x 44 1/2; Mylar (Box FD 7, Folder F17)
  - Victory Loan - Battleships, undated; Size (in inches): 29 1/2 x 39; Publisher: Powers Co Litho, NY; L.A. Shafer (Box FD 8, Folder 0.001)
  - YMCA (Services), 1919; Size (in inches): 41 x 28; Publisher: NP; Albert Herter (Box FD 8, Folder 0.002)
  - Victory Loan, undated; Size (in inches): 40 x 27; Publisher: Forbes Boston; Howard Chandler Christy (Box FD 8, Folder 0.003)
  - Come On!, 1918; Size (in inches): 30 x 20; Publisher: Ketterlinus, Phila.; Walter Whitehead (Box FD 8, Folder 0.004)
  - Bonds with Sun, undated; Size (in inches): 28 x 22; Publisher: NP; NA (Box FD 8, Folder 0.005)
  - Loan with Handprint, undated; Size (in inches): 30 x 19 3/4; Publisher: Manz Engraving, Chicago; J. Allen St. John (Box FD 8, Folder 0.006)
  - Liberty Loan, 1918; Size (in inches): 38 x 25 3/4; Publisher: Edwards & Deutsch Litho Co. Chicago; Gerrit A. Beneker (Box FD 8, Folder 0.009)
  - 3rd Liberty Loan, undated; Size (in inches): 30 x 20; Publisher: Sackett & Wilhelm, NY; Lawrence Harris Dup. (Box FD 8, Folder 0.01)
  - Navy Recruitment, 1917; Size (in inches): 30 x 24; Publisher: Dup. 1973 reproduction; Howard Chandler Christy (Box FD 8, Folder 0.011)
  - Home and Country, 1918; Size (in inches): 30 x 20; Publisher: American Lithographic Co., NY; Alfred Everett Orr (Box FD 8, Folder 0.012)
  - YMCA/YWCA, undated; Size (in inches): 21 1/2 x 41 (Box FD 8, Folder 0.013)
  - Come On!, 1918; Size (in inches): 30 x 20; Publisher: Ketterlinus, PA; Walter Whitehead (Box FD 8, Folder 0.014)
  - Invest, undated; Size (in inches): 30 x 19 1/2; Publisher: Strobridge Litho. Co. Cincinnati (Box FD 8, Folder 0.015)
  - Lend, undated; Size (in inches): 19 x 27 1/2 (Box FD 8, Folder 0.016)
  - Navy Bonds, undated; Size (in inches): 30 x 20; Publisher: Forbes Boston; Howard Chandler Christy (Box FD 8, Folder 0.017)
  - Red Cross Christmas, 1918; Size (in inches): 28 x 19; E. H. Blashfield (Box FD 8, Folder 0.018)
  - Home and Country, 1918; Size (in inches): 30 x 20; Publisher: American Lithographic Co, NY; Alfred Everett Orr (Box FD 8, Folder 0.019)
  - Wilson - Red Cross, 1918; Size (in inches): 27 1/2 x 20; Publisher: U.S. Printing & Lithograph Co., NY; Mielziner (Box FD 8, Folder 0.02)
  - Salvation Army, undated; Size (in inches): 28 X 21; Publisher: Libbie Printing Co., 259 Dover St., Boston (Box FD 8, Folder 0.022)
  - 2nd Liberty Loan, 1917; Size (in inches): 30 x 20; Publisher: Edwards & Deutsch Litho Co. Chicago; Dup. (Box FD 8, Folder 0.023)
  - Belgium - Bonds, undated; Size (in inches): 30 x 20; Publisher: United States Printing & Litho. Co., NY; Ellsworth Young (Box FD 8, Folder 0.024)
  - Red Cross, 1918; Size (in inches): 28 x 21; Publisher: American Red Cross; Jessie Wilcox Smith (Box FD 8, Folder 0.024)
  - Christmas Red Cross, undated; Size (in inches): 30 X 20 (Box FD 8, Folder 0.025)
  - Red Cross, 1918; Size (in inches): 30 x 20; Publisher: American Red Cross; Ray Greenleaf (Box FD 8, Folder 0.026)
  - Liberty Loan Children, 1917; Size (in inches): 30 x 20; Publisher: T.F. Moore CO., NY; Dewey (Box FD 8, Folder 0.027)
  - Liberty Bonds, undated; Size (in inches): 29 1/2 x 19 3/4; Publisher: Edwards & Deutsch Litho Co. Chicago (Box FD 8, Folder 0.028)
  - YMCA War Work, undated; Size (in inches): 27 1/2 X 19 3/4; Gil Spear (Box FD 8, Folder 0.029)
  - War Camp (piano), undated; Size (in inches): 30 x 20; Publisher: Heywood Strauser & Voight Litho Co., NY; NA (Box FD 8, Folder 0.031)
  - YMCA For Your Boy, 1918; Size (in inches): 30 x 20; Publisher: Ketterlinus, Phila.; Arthur William Brown (Box FD 8, Folder 0.031)
  - War Campaign, 1918; Size (in inches): 30 x 20; Publisher: National Catholic War Council; Burton Rice (Box FD 8, Folder 0.032)
  - United War Work Campaign, undated; Size (in inches): 30 x 20; NA (Box FD 8, Folder 0.032)
  - War Bonds, undated; Size (in inches): 30 19; Haskell Coffin (Box FD 8, Folder 0.033)
  - Red Cross, undated; Size (in inches): 27 1/4 x20 3/4; Publisher: C. Rosserod Chambers; Mylar (Box FD 8, Folder *)
  - Third Liberty Loan, 1917; Size (in inches): 40 x 30; Publisher: Forbes Boston; Howard Chandler Christy (Box FD 8, Folder *)
  - Library Loan - Children, undated; Size (in inches): 30 x 20; Publisher: United States Printing & Litho. Co., NY; Mylar (Box FD 8, Folder *)
  - Disabled, 1921; Size (in inches): 27 1/4 x 21; Mylar (Box FD 8, Folder *)
  - 3rd Liberty Loan (Boy Scout), undated; Size (in inches): 30 x 20; Publisher: American Lithographic Co, NY; Mylar (Box FD 8, Folder *)
  - Third Liberty Loan, undated; Size (in inches): 36 x 56; Publisher: Edwards & Deutsch Litho Co. Chicago; Herbert Paus (Box FD 8, Folder *)
  - Home and Country, 1918; Size (in inches): 40 x 30; Publisher: American Lithographic Co, NY; Alfred Everett Orr, Mylar (Box FD 8, Folder *)
- World War II
  - War Bonds, undated; Size (in inches): 25 x 14; Publisher: Coulter; Dup. (Box FD 7, Folder F2)
  - Christmas War Bonds, undated; Size (in inches): 26 x 18 1/2; Publisher: U.S. Treasury Dept.; Linn Ball (Box FD 7, Folder F2)
  - War Bonds 1950, undated; Size (in inches): 18 1/2 x 26; Publisher: U.S. Treasury Dept. (Box FD 7, Folder F2)
  - Banner, undated; Size (in inches): 17 x 120; Publisher: Office of Emerg. Management (Box FD 7, Folder F3)
  - Banner, undated; Size (in inches): 17 x 120; Publisher: Office of Emerg. Management (Box FD 7, Folder F3)
  - Buy Early, undated; Size (in inches): 20 x 27 (Box FD 7, Folder F3)
  - Show Your Button, undated; Size (in inches): 27 1/2 x 20 1/2 (Box FD 7, Folder F3)
  - Liberty Bond Storage, undated; Size (in inches): 22 X 16 (Box FD 7, Folder F3)
  - "V", undated; Size (in inches): 29 3/4 x 19 1/2 (Box FD 7, Folder F3)
  - Recruitment Poster, undated; Size (in inches): 23 x 24 1/4; Publisher: Navy Aviation (Box FD 7, Folder F4)
  - 6th War Loan, 1944; Size (in inches): 40 x 28 1/2; Publisher: U.S. Treasury Dept. (Box FD 7, Folder F4)
  - War Bonds, 1945; Size (in inches): 40 x 28 1/2; Publisher: U.S. Treasury Dept. (Box FD 7, Folder F4)
  - Christmas War Bonds, 1944; Size (in inches): 38 x 28 1/2; Publisher: U.S. Treasury Dept.; Lyman Simpson (Box FD 7, Folder F4)
  - Navy Day, 1946; Size (in inches): 40 x 28 (Box FD 7, Folder F4)
  - Jobs in the Army Air Force, 1942; Size (in inches): 28 1/4 x 39; Publisher: Fed. Sec. Agcy., Dept. of Educ. (Box FD 7, Folder F4)
  - Homeakers War Guide, 1942; Size (in inches): 28 x 22; Publisher: Office of War Information; Mylar Dup. (Box FD 7, Folder F5)
  - War Jobs, 1942; Size (in inches): 27 x 19 1/2 (Box FD 7, Folder F5)
  - Farm Work, undated; Size (in inches): 18 1/2 x 12 1/2 (Box FD 7, Folder F5)
  - Red Cross, 1943; Size (in inches): 28 x 22; Publisher: Schliker (?) '43 (Box FD 7, Folder F5)
  - Forest Fires, 1943; Size (in inches): 25 x 22; Publisher: USDA State Forest Service (Box FD 7, Folder F5)
  - School Poster WWII, undated; Size (in inches): 22 x 16; Publisher: US Treas. For F.W. Woolworth (Box FD 7, Folder F5)
  - Christmas War Bonds, 1942; Size (in inches): 28 x 22 (Box FD 7, Folder F5)
  - War Jobs, 1943; Size (in inches): 28 x 22; Publisher: Office of War Information (Box FD 7, Folder F5)
  - Labor - Team Work, 1943; Size (in inches): 21 x 13; Publisher: Work Production Drive (Box FD 7, Folder F5)
  - Liberty Loan, undated; Size (in inches): 21 X 14 (Box FD 7, Folder F5)
  - National War Fund, undated; Size (in inches): 42 x 28; Publisher: Douglas Las (?) (Box FD 7, Folder F5)
  - Civilian Defense, 1941; Size (in inches): 40 x 30; Publisher: Photo by Arthur. H. Fisher (Box FD 7, Folder F5)
  - Men Working, 1941; Size (in inches): 30 x 40; Publisher: Office of Emerg. Management (Box FD 7, Folder F5)
  - Food Message - Truman, 1946; Size (in inches): 18 1/4 x 26; Publisher: US Dept. of Agriculture (Box FD 7, Folder F6)
  - Price Warning, 1945; Size (in inches): 26 x 18 1/4; Publisher: US Office of Price Admin. (Box FD 7, Folder F6)
  - Price Control, 1944; Size (in inches): 22 1/2 x 17; Publisher: US Office of Price Admin. (Box FD 7, Folder F6)
  - Price Control, 1945; Size (in inches): 22 1/2 x 17; Publisher: US Office of Price Admin. (Box FD 7, Folder F6)
  - Price Control, 1945; Size (in inches): 22 x 17; Publisher: US Office of Price Admin. (Box FD 7, Folder F6)
  - Meats Price Control, 1944; Size (in inches): 17 x 22; Publisher: US Office of Price Admin. (Box FD 7, Folder F6)
  - OPA Poster, 1944; Size (in inches): 28 x 20; Publisher: US Office of Price Admin. (Box FD 7, Folder F6)
  - Rent Control, 1946; Size (in inches): 26 x 18 1/4; Publisher: US Office of Price Admin. (Box FD 7, Folder F6)
  - Red Cross Blood Drive, undated; Size (in inches): 14 x 11; Publisher: Red Cross Natl. Blood Program; Mylar (Box FD 7, Folder F7)
  - Farm Work, undated; Size (in inches): 18 1/2 x 12 1/4; Publisher: International Harvester; Mylar (Box FD 7, Folder F7)
  - School Stamps and Bonds, undated; Size (in inches): 22 x 13 1/2; Publisher: US Treas. Dept., Howard (artist); Mylar Dup. (Box FD 7, Folder F7)
  - Junior Red Cross, undated; Size (in inches): 22 1/2 x 14 1/2; Publisher: Amos Sewell; Mylar Dup. (Box FD 7, Folder F7)
  - Farm Volunteers, 1945; Size (in inches): 26 x 18 1/2; Publisher: US Crop Corp, Victory Farm Vol.; Anton Bruell, Mylar (Box FD 7, Folder F7)
  - Paper Salvage, undated; Size (in inches): 28 x 20; Mylar Dup. (Box FD 7, Folder F7)
  - Milk Weed Pods, 1944; Size (in inches): 14 1/4 x 11 1/4; Publisher: County War Board Exten. Serv. (Box FD 7, Folder F7)
  - War Bonds, 1946; Size (in inches): 26 x 18 1/2; Elmo White (Box FD 7, Folder F7)
  - Junior Red Cross, undated; Size (in inches): 22 1/12 x 14 1/2; Publisher: A. Parker (Box FD 7, Folder F7)
  - School Savings, undated; Size (in inches): 21 1/2 x 13 3/4; Publisher: US Treasury Dept. (Box FD 7, Folder F7)
  - Farm Volunteers, 1944; Size (in inches): 28 x 20 1/4; Publisher: US Crop Corp, Victory Farm Vol. (Box FD 7, Folder F7)
  - School Stamps and Bonds, undated; Size (in inches): 22 X 13 1/2; Publisher: Div. Info., Office Emerg. Mgmt. (Box FD 7, Folder F7)
  - Defense Production, undated; Size (in inches): 20 x 14; Publisher: Nat. Comm. Consv. Man Power (Box FD 7, Folder F9)
  - Savings Bonds: Minuteman, 1946; Size (in inches): 28 x 18 1/2; Publisher: US Treasury Dept. (Box FD 7, Folder F9)
  - Fifth War Loan, 1944; Size (in inches): 28 x 20; Publisher: "Memory of USS Dorado"; Schrieber '44 (Box FD 7, Folder F9)
  - Wounded Soldier, 1945; Size (in inches): 26 x 18 1/2; Publisher: US Treasury Dept.; Adolph Treidler (Box FD 7, Folder F9)
  - Civilian Defense, 1941; Size (in inches): 28 x 22 1/4; Publisher: Div. Info., Office Emerg. Mgmt. (Box FD 7, Folder F9)
  - Buy War Bonds: Minuteman, 1943; Size (in inches): 14 x 11; JA (Box FD 7, Folder F9)
  - 3rd War Loan: Attack, 1943; Size (in inches): 14 x 10 (Box FD 7, Folder F9)
  - Bonds Build Ships, 1943; Size (in inches): 15 3/4 x 11; Publisher: Abbott Lab Treasury School Prog; George Picken (Box FD 7, Folder F9)
  - Army Air Force, 1944; Size (in inches): 25 x 19; Publisher: War Department; Schlaikier (Box FD 7, Folder F9)
  - Savings Bonds: Resolution, 1945; Size (in inches): 26 x 18 1/2; Publisher: US Treasury Dept. (Box FD 7, Folder F9)
  - Air Rid Warning System, 1943; Size (in inches): 20 x 28; Publisher: Office of Civil Defense (Box FD 7, Folder F9)
  - G.I. Bill, undated; Size (in inches): 25 x 17; Publisher: Recruit Publcty Bureau, US Army (Box FD 7, Folder F9)
  - Christmas War Bonds, undated; Size (in inches): 26 X 18 1/2; Publisher: US Treasury Dept.; Linn Ball, Dup. (Box FD 7, Folder F9)
  - School Stamps, undated; Size (in inches): 22 x 14; Boulter, Mylar (Box FD 7, Folder F9)
  - School Stamps and Bonds (Citizenship), 1952; Size (in inches): 26 x 18 1/2; Mylar (Box FD 7, Folder F9)
  - Bonds at School (Flag and Farm), 1945; Size (in inches): 26 x 18 1/2; Publisher: US Treasury Dept.; George Kanelous, Mylar (Box FD 7, Folder F9)
  - OPA Price Control, 1943; Size (in inches): 40 x 28 1/2; Publisher: Office of Price Administration (Box FD 7, Folder F10)
  - UN Charter, undated; Size (in inches): 37 x 26 (Box FD 7, Folder F10)
  - News Map, 1945; Size (in inches): 35 x 40 1/2; Publisher: Bur. Pub. Relations, War Dept. (Box FD 7, Folder F11)
  - Milk Weed, undated; Size (in inches): 14 1/4 x 11 1/4; Mylar Dup. (Box FD 7, Folder F12)
  - War Bonds, undated; Size (in inches): 15 1/2 x 11; Publisher: Abbott Lab, US Treasury Dept.; Joseph Hirsch, Mylar (Box FD 7, Folder F12)
  - Victory Loan, 1945; Size (in inches): 26 x 18 1/2; Dean Cornwell (Box FD 7, Folder F12)
  - Victory Loan (with FDR), 1945; Size (in inches): 26 x 18 1/2; Publisher: U.S. Treasury Dept.; S. C. Berll (?) (Box FD 7, Folder F12)
  - Rationing Chart, 1942; Size (in inches): 22 x 28; Mylar (Box FD 7, Folder F14)
  - Roosevelt Quotation, 1943; Size (in inches): 14 x 20; Publisher: Office of War Information; Mylar (Box FD 7, Folder F14)
  - Public Warning 1942, Size (in inches): 20 x 14 1/2; Publisher: Office of War Information; Ericson, Mylar (Box FD 7, Folder F14)
  - Third War Loan (Attack), 1943; Size (in inches): 28 x 20; Dup. (Box FD 7, Folder F14)
  - Soldiers "1776-1943", Size (in inches): 40 x 28 1/2; Publisher: Office of War Information; B. Perlin (Box FD 7, Folder F14)
  - War Bonds 1950, 1943; Size (in inches): 40 x 28 1/2; Robert Sloan (Box FD 7, Folder F14)
  - Rationing (with GI), 1943; Size (in inches): 28 x 22; Publisher: Office of War Information (Box FD 7, Folder F14)
  - War Bonds (Declaration), 1942; Size (in inches): 28 x 22; Publisher: Victory Display Committee (Box FD 7, Folder F15)
  - Army Insignia, undated; Size (in inches): 20 x 20; Dup. 1 Mylar, 1 plain (Box FD 7, Folder F16)
  - Boy Scouts, undated; Size (in inches): 28 x 21; Publisher: Lutz & Sheinmar Liths., NY; Norman Rockwell, Mylar (Box FD 7, Folder F17)
  - Freedom From Want, undated; Size (in inches): 40 x 28 1/2; Publisher: Office of War Information; Norman Rockwell, Mylar (Box FD 7, Folder F18)
  - Freedom of Speech, 1943; Size (in inches): 40 x 28 1/2; Publisher: Office of War Information; Norman Rockwell, Mylar (Box FD 7, Folder F18)
  - Freedom of Worship, 1943; Size (in inches): 40 x 28 1/2; Publisher: Office of War Information; Norman Rockwell, Mylar (Box FD 7, Folder F18)
  - Freedom From Fear, 1943; Size (in inches): 40 x 28 1/2; Publisher: Office of War Information; Norman Rockwell, Mylar (Box FD 7, Folder F18)
  - War Bond (Uncle Sam), 1942; Size (in inches): 14 x 11 (Box FD 7, Folder F17)
  - Schools at War Program, 1942; Size (in inches): 28 x 22; Publisher: U.S. Treasury Dept.; Irving Nurick, Mylar (Box FD 7, Folder F17)
  - Red Cross, undated; Size (in inches): 33 1/2 x 21; Publisher: Toni Frissell (Box FD 8, Folder 0.021)
  - Victory at Home, undated; Size (in inches): 40 x 30; Publisher: Navy Department; Howard Scott, USNR, Mylar (Box FD 8, Folder No #)
  - Torpodoes, undated; Size (in inches): 22 x 17; Publisher: Salvage Div., War Production; McClelland Barklay, USNR (Box FD 8, Folder F19)
  - Can Drive, undated; Size (in inches): 33 1/4 x 24 1/2 (Box FD 8, Folder 0.033)
  - Nazi Brutality, 1942; Size (in inches): 38 x 28 1/4; Publisher: Office of War Information; Ben Shahan (Box FD 8, Folder 0.034)
  - War Bonds (Air Force), 1943; Size (in inches): 40 x 28 1/2; Publisher: NP; Schreiber (Box FD 8, Folder 0.036)
  - War Bonds (Buy), 1943; Size (in inches): 40 x 28 1/2; Publisher: NP; JA (Box FD 8, Folder 0.036)
  - Saving Fats, 1943; Size (in inches): 42 x 29; Publisher: NP; NA (Box FD 8, Folder 0.037)
  - WAAC, 1943; Size (in inches): 28 x 22; Publisher: Recruiting Publicity Bureau; NA, Mylar (Box FD 8, Folder 0.038)
  - War Bonds, 1943; Size (in inches): 28 1/4 x 22; Publisher: NP; NA (Box FD 8, Folder 0.039)
  - Buy Bonds, 1950; Size (in inches): 18 1/2 x 26; Publisher: U.S. Treasury Dept.; Garry Orr, Mylar (Box FD 8)
  - Women at War, 1942; Size (in inches): 40 x 28; Publisher: War Man Power Commission; NA, Mylar (Box FD 8)
  - WWII Gratitude, undated; Size (in inches): 33 1/2 x 23 1/2; Publisher: American Oil Company; NA (Box FD 8, Folder 0.04)
  - War Bonds, 1942; Size (in inches): 28 x 22; Publisher: NP; NA (Box FD 8, Folder 0.042)
  - Yankee Subs, undated; Size (in inches): 30 x 22; Publisher: NP; NA (Box FD 8, Folder 0.043)
  - United Nations, 1942; Size (in inches): 28 x 22; Publisher: Office of War Information; Broder (Box FD 8, Folder 0.044)
  - United We Win, 1943; Size (in inches): 28 x 22; Publisher: Office of War Information; Liberman (Box FD 8, Folder 0.045)
  - Five Sullivans, 1943; Size (in inches): 28 x 22; Publisher: Office of War Information; NA, Mylar (Box FD 8, Folder 0.041)
  - Christmas War Bonds, 1941; Size (in inches): 27 1/2 x 21 1/4; Publisher: NP; Wilbinsons (Box FD 8, Folder 0.05)
  - Freedom From Want, 1943; Size (in inches): 28 x 20; Publisher: Office of War Information; Rockwell (Box FD 8, Folder 0.049)
  - Use It Up, 1943; Size (in inches): 28 x 22; Publisher: Office of War Information; Mylar (Box FD 8, Folder 0.048)
  - Invasion Bond, 1944; Size (in inches): 20 x 27 3/4; Publisher: U.S. Treasury Dept.; R. Moore, Mylar (Box FD 8, Folder 0.047)
  - Scrap Drive, 1942; Size (in inches): 28 x 20; Publisher: NP; F. Eroder, Mylar (Box FD 8, Folder 0.047)
  - Victory Garden, 1943; Size (in inches): 28 x 22; Publisher: Office of War Information; NA, Mylar (Box FD 8, Folder 0.046)